//Subject of the Quiz
const subject = "The Pittsburgh Steelers";

// Question Content
const questionContent = [
  {
    question: "In the Steelers first Super Bowl appearance, who did they defeat?",
    choice1: "Los Angeles Rams",
    choice2: "Dallas Cowboys",
    choice3: "St. Louis Cardinals",
    choice4: "Minnesota Vikings",
    correct: "Minnesota Vikings",
    source: "Source: https://www.funtrivia.com/trivia-quiz/Sports/All-About-the-Steelers-2-292556.html"
  },
  {
    question: "In Pittsburgh's first year in the National Football League, what was their team name?",
    choice1: "Iron Men",
    choice2: "Keystoners",
    choice3: "Pirates",
    choice4: "Steagles",
    correct: "Pirates",
    source: "Source: https://www.funtrivia.com/trivia-quiz/Sports/All-About-the-Steelers-1-291616.html"
  },
  {
    question: "What year did the Pittsburgh Steelers win their first Super Bowl?",
    choice1: "1975",
    choice2: "1974",
    choice3: "1978",
    choice4: "1972",
    correct: "1975",
    source: "Source: https://www.funtrivia.com/trivia-quiz/Sports/A-Dynasty-To-Remember-279280.html"
  },
  {
    question: "After the 2006 season, which Steeler head coach stepped down after 15 seasons?",
    choice1: "Buddy Austin",
    choice2: "Chuck Noll",
    choice3: "Bill Austin",
    choice4: "Bill Cowher",
    correct: "Bill Cowher",
    source: "Source:  https://www.funtrivia.com/trivia-quiz/Sports/Your-Pittsburgh-Steelers-271049.html"
  },
  {
    question: "In which year, did Art Rooney Sr. purchase the NFL franchise that would become the Pittsburgh Steelers?",
    choice1: "1935",
    choice2: "1946",
    choice3: "1933",
    choice4: "1942",
    correct: "1933",
    source: "Source: https://www.funtrivia.com/trivia-quiz/Sports/Steelers-History-131736.html"
  },
  {
    question: "Who coached the Steelers to four Super Bowl wins in the 1970s seasons?",
    choice1: "Chuck Noll",
    choice2: "Bill Cowher",
    choice3: "Terry Bradshaw",
    choice4: "Joe Green",
    correct: "Chuck Noll",
    source: "Source:  https://www.funtrivia.com/trivia-quiz/Sports/A-Dynasty-To-Remember-279280.html"
  },
  {
    question: "Who caught the ball during the play called the Immaculate Reception?",
    choice1: "Lynn Swan",
    choice2: "Franco Harris",
    choice3: "John Fuqua",
    choice4: "Jack Ham",
    correct: "Franco Harris",
  },
  {
    question: "The Steelers ruled the NFL in the 1970s by winning four Super Bowls. Which team did they defeat twice in the big one in the decade?",
    choice1: "Oakland Raiders",
    choice2: "Minnesota Vikings",
    choice3: "Dallas Cowboys",
    choice4: "Denver Broncos",
    correct: "Dallas Cowboys",
    source: "Source:  https://www.funtrivia.com/trivia-quiz/Sports/Your-Pittsburgh-Steelers-271049.html"
  },
  {
    question: "How many Super Bowl titles do the Pittsburgh Steelers have?",
    choice1: "3",
    choice2: "5",
    choice3: "6",
    choice4: "7",
    correct: "6",
    source: "Source:  https://operations.nfl.com/learn-the-game/nfl-basics/team-histories/american-football-conference/north/pittsburgh-steelers/#:~:text=Team%20History,made%20the%20playoffs%20eight%20times."
  },
  {
    question: "Which Pittsburgh Steeler quarterback has the most yards passed in their careers?",
    choice1: "Ben Roethlisberger",
    choice2: "Terry Bradshaw",
    choice3: "Bubby Brister",
    choice4: "Neil O'Donnell",
    correct: "Ben Roethlisberger",
    source: "Source:  https://www.profootballhof.com/teams/pittsburgh-steelers/team-facts/"
  },
];

